<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on OSSTD doc</title>
    <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on OSSTD doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:36:35 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Create prototype model</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userguide/quick_start/create_prototyp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 15:43:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userguide/quick_start/create_prototyp/</guid>
      <description>Create a prototype model OpenStudio Standard package embedded code to generate OpenStudio version of prototype buildings. This quick tutorial will create a prototype building and run the ASHRAE 90.1-2019 Appendix G (PRM) automation process.
To begin with, we need to import both packages.
require &amp;#39;openstudio&amp;#39; require &amp;#39;openstudio-standard&amp;#39; You can use require_relative [ABSOLUTE_PATH] to import the OSSTD source code if you choose to use the package from Github.
Next, we want to create a MediumOffice prototype building in climate zone 4A (New York) that is designed following the 90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baseline automation</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userguide/quick_start/baseline_automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userguide/quick_start/baseline_automation/</guid>
      <description>This quick tutorial will generate an ASHRAE 90.1-2019 Appendix G baseline from a medium office prototype.
In the previous step, we created a medium office prototype model in Climate zone 4. In this section, let&amp;rsquo;s write the script to generate a baseline for this prototype building. First, we need to import openstudio and openstudio-standards packages.
require &amp;#39;openstudio&amp;#39; require &amp;#39;openstudio-standard&amp;#39; Next, load the model and prepare compliance parameters for baseline generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More_examples</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userguide/quick_start/more_examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 09:36:35 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userguide/quick_start/more_examples/</guid>
      <description>This section will walk through an additional script that alters our prototype model before running the baseline.
OpenStudio Standard package is a powerful package that allows user to manipulate their models with simple commands - particularly high-level HVAC templates and model data modifications.
In this section, we will use the OpenStudio Standard package to:
Reset window to wall ratio to 60% Add overhangs to the south facade Replace the HVAC system with DOAS + water source heat pumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Requirements</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/installation/requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 16:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/installation/requirements/</guid>
      <description>You will need following applications to ensure OpenStudio Standard running smoothly on your project.
Ruby version support Officially Ruby 2.7. Latest stable version is 2.7.6 and it can be downloaded at: https://cache.ruby-lang.org/pub/ruby/2.7/ruby-2.7.6.tar.gz
Follow the installation guide to complete the ruby installation. You can also verify the ruby installation with the following command in command line:
C:\Users\sample_user&amp;gt;ruby -v ruby 2.7.4p191 (2021-07-07 revision a21a3b7d23) [x64-mingw32] OpenStudio OpenStudio 3.2. The latest stable 3.2 version is 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exterior Lights</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userdata/data_forms/exterior_lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 16:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/userdata/data_forms/exterior_lights/</guid>
      <description>User Data CSV File: user_data_exterior_lights.csv
Each exterior lights object in the model can be assigned up to nine exterior lighting subcategories in the user data file based on Appendix G Table G3.6. The lighting subcategories are designated by the labels:
end_use_subcategory_01
through
end_use_subcategory_09
For each subcategory, the appropriate quantity must also be listed, as designated by:
end_use_measurement_value_01
through
end_use_measurement_value_09
The units of the measurement value are indicated by the last part of the subcategory name:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/installation/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 16:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/installation/installation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dev_instruction</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/dev_instruction/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 15:43:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/dev_instruction/</guid>
      <description>Image Images uses relative links to the local images folder (in the same level as the markdown file). A preceding exclamation point is needed.
![PNNL Campus](/BEM-for-PRM/basics/images/PNNL_campus.jpg) You can adjust the image size by using the css width and/or height to the link image.
![PNNL Campus](/BEM-for-PRM/basics/images/PNNL_campus.jpg?width=200px) And add CSS (border) to it
![PNNL Campus](/BEM-for-PRM/basics/images/PNNL_campus.jpg?width=200px&amp;amp;classes=border) Tips/Notes/Warnings Note A notice disclaimer
Code # Template method for adding a setpoint manager for a coil control logic to a heating coil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
