<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on OSSTD doc</title>
    <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on OSSTD doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:50 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Appendix G PRM Rules</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/capabilities/rules_appendix_g_prm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/capabilities/rules_appendix_g_prm/</guid>
      <description> Appendix G Performance Rating Method Rules and OSSTD-PRM The &amp;ldquo;Create ASHRAE 90.1-2019 PRM Model&amp;rdquo; measure provides a detailed implementation of the rules of the Appendix G Performance Rating Method. Below are some of the key changes that are applied by the tool when creating the Baseline model:
Apply baseline envelope rules Space conditioning type Constructions Insulation levels Window-to-wall ratio Skylight-to-roof ratio Infiltration Apply baseline lighting rules Lighting power Lighting occupancy sensor control Determine and create baseline HVAC systems Remove user model HVAC Determine baseline HVAC based on building type and Appendix G rules Create new baseline HVAC systems Apply special rules for computer rooms and laboratories Size HVAC systems Apply HVAC efficiencies Apply fan power adjustments Apply baseline HVAC controls Rotate building model through cardinal directions Check for unmet load hours and rectify, if needed Handle additional compliance data Multiple building types Plug load measures Elevators Exterior lighting Interior lighting exceptions Number of systems per zone </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limitations</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/limitations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:48:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/limitations/</guid>
      <description>Chapter 1.3 Limitations of OSSTD-PRM Some features of 90.1-2019 Appendix G that have not yet been implemented into the baseline automation are summarized below.
Features System Item Baseline Model vs. Proposed Model Notes HVAC components Humidification Same as proposed model in the tool. In some cases, the baseline is required to be changed to adiabatic humidification. This has not been implemented Humidification For constant volume systems, Appendix G indicates that only 25% of the system reheat energy shall be included in the budget building performance This is not yet implemented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/features/benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/features/benefits/</guid>
      <description>There are various benefits of using OSSTD-PRM, some of them include: Stable Foundation for User and Third-Party Tools: The OSSTD-PRM offers a dependable platform not only for existing users but also for third-party Building Energy Modeling (BEM) tools. Simultaneously, it encourages the creation of new applications that harness its capabilities.
Enhanced Runtime Execution: This measure results in improved runtime execution, leading to faster and more efficient processes for users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Use Cases and Applications</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/capabilities/use_case_applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/capabilities/use_case_applications/</guid>
      <description>Here are some use cases for the OSSTD-PRM Energy Modelers
Energy modelers can utilize the OSSTD-PRM measure to automate the creation of baseline building models. They can also refer to the PRM-RM (Performance Rating Method Reference Manual) for guidelines on how to generate models for proposed designs. This can streamline the energy modeling process and ensure consistency and compliance with relevant standards.
BEM Software Vendors/Developers
Building energy modeling software vendors and developers can incorporate the measure and methodology into their workflow to automatically generate baseline building models while ensuring the neutrality of schedules and other modeling assumptions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planned Features</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/features/planned_features/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/features/planned_features/</guid>
      <description> Coming Soon&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get OpenStudio App</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_app/get_os_app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_app/get_os_app/</guid>
      <description>A. Install the OpenStudio App following these steps. Download the latest release of OpenStudio application from OpenStudio Coalition GitHub page. Select the installer that matches your operating system.
The OpenStudio engine as well as other components (e.g., EnergyPlus, Ruby API, etc..) are included in the installation package.
For more information, refer to the installation instructions by the OpenStudio Coalition.
The following table shows a compatibility matrix for OpenStudio application and &amp;ldquo;Create ASHRAE 90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install the measure</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_app/install_measure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:51:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_app/install_measure/</guid>
      <description>B. Install the OSSTD &amp;ldquo;Create ASHRAE 90.1-2019 PRM Model&amp;rdquo; measure using any of the following approaches. The PRM measure can be downloaded using two different approaches.
1. Download measure from the documentation website The &amp;ldquo;Create ASHRAE 90.1-2019 PRM Model&amp;rdquo; measure can be downloaded from measures.zip (7 KB)
After downloading the measure, unzip the folder.
Copy/Move the CreateBaselineBuilding measure folder to the local Measures directory used by the OpenStudio App. You can check the measures directory by clicking on Change My Measures Directory under the Preferences tab of the OS app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run the measure</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_app/how_run_measure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:52:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_app/how_run_measure/</guid>
      <description>C. Run the measure in OS App Before running the measure, review the model requirements in Model Requirements
graph LR; A(1.Navigate to Measures tab) --&gt; B(*2. Optional Step* Check measure directory) B --&gt; C(3.Select measure) C --&gt; D(4.Adjust measure inputs) D --&gt; E(5.Run simulation) Navigate to the Measures tab from the vertical list on the left side of the interface. Optional: Check that the measure exists in the local measures directory by clicking on the my folder at the bottom right corner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get OpenStudio SDK</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/get_openstudio_sdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/get_openstudio_sdk/</guid>
      <description>A. Install the correct version of OpenStudio SDK Download the latest release of OpenStudio SDK from OpenStudio Releases GitHub page. Select the installer that matches your operating system.
The OpenStudio SDK installation package contains OpenStudio-Standards, EnergyPlus as well as other components (e.g., Ruby 2.7, etc..).
For more installation information, refer to the OpenStudio Github page.
Information about OpenStudio SDK CLI, refer to the Command Line Interface (CLI).
The following table shows a compatibility matrix for OpenStudio SDK and &amp;ldquo;Create ASHRAE 90.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run the measure</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_the_measure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_the_measure/</guid>
      <description>B. Run the measure with OS SDK using CLI There are 5 parts in the process of running the measure.
Download the PRM measure (prerequisite) Setup a local directory Edit OSW file Execute the measure Save the Output 1. Download the PRM measure Download measure in the link below: Create Baseline Building: measures.zip (7 KB) Refer to Install the measure for other installation options.
2. Setup a local directory Setup a local directory to include all required inputs (the following example is one way to setup the directory):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run measure w/ OSSTD Package</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_measure_with_osstd_package/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_measure_with_osstd_package/</guid>
      <description>C. Steps to run the measure with OSSTD Package (Optional) This instruction is provided for users who want to access the latest features or bug fixes that are not accessible in the latest OpenStudio SDK.
Follow the steps from Run the measure instruction by replacing the Setup (Step 2) and Execution steps (Step 4) as mentioned below.
Setup Download this openstudio-standards package. Unzip the package to a local directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installation</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_engine/installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:01:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_engine/installation/</guid>
      <description>A. Steps to install and get the OpenStudio PRM running for scripting with OpenStudio API There are 4 parts to this section.
Download Ruby Download OpenStudio Connect Ruby with OpenStudio Download OpenStudio Standard 1. Download Ruby Ruby 2.7. Compatible version is 2.7.2 and it can be downloaded at: https://cache.ruby-lang.org/pub/ruby/2.7/ruby-2.7.2.tar.gz
You can verify the ruby installation with the following command in the command line: C:\Users\sample_user&amp;gt;ruby -v ruby 2.7.2p137 (2020-10-01 revision 5445e04352) [x64-mingw32] 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call measure via API</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_engine/call_use_api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:00:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_engine/call_use_api/</guid>
      <description>B. Here is a quick overview of calling the measure via the API method The steps that generate baseline model(s) from a provided openstudio model are as follows:
Create stable baseline building API User data Baseline outputs 1. Create stable baseline building API The ASHRAE 90.1-2019 PRM automation can be called in a Ruby script via its API method create a baseline model from a proposed model. The API method provides great flexibility for creating customized modeling workflow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo 1: Geometry</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo1/</guid>
      <description>Demo 1 shows geometry transformations in a user model The proposed model (as shown in the image) is a typical medium sized office building with roughly 60% window-to-wall ratio (WWR) and overhangs on its south facade. The default_hvac_bldg_type is set to other nonresidential, and the window to wall ratio and service water heating system building types are both set according to the related category. The building is assumed to be located in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo 2: HVAC</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo2/</guid>
      <description>Demo 2 shows HVAC transformations in a user model In Demo 2, we have a medium office user model with an area of 52000 sqft. It is equipped with water source heat pumps for heating and cooling and a DOAS for ventilation (as shown in the image below). Also, the Core Top Zone is being identified as a high equipment density (40 W/m2) room.
According to the ASHRAE 90.1 PRM method - &amp;ldquo;Baseline HVAC System Types&amp;rdquo; table, the baseline system type for the medium office that satisfies the requirements - Other residential + 5 floors or fewer and 25000ft2 to 150,000ft2, shall be a packaged VAV with reheat (system 5).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo 3: User Data</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo3/</guid>
      <description>Demo 3 shows how to provide additional user data for the PRM function In Demo 3, we will demonstrate how to input user data to handle multiple building types in a model.
Download the folder &amp;ldquo;demo3_zip&amp;rdquo; on your system and extract it in any local folder (to be changed based on the method used in the sections below). The zip file contains the model (.osm), user data (.csv) and weather file (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/best_practices/</guid>
      <description>Here are some best practices to run the PRM measure: The space types should be defined in the model : The lighting space type is used to determine the baseline lighting power density and lighting control savings. Read more about it in Standards space type section. If the User Compliance Data files contain lighting space type assignments, there is a hierachy for determining the final assignments:
user_data_space is first priority user_data_space_type is second priority StandardsSpaceType property of the SpaceType objest is lowest priority Dates in the schedule must have a &amp;ldquo;MM/DD&amp;rdquo; formatting : Where is this inserted?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standards space type</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/standards_space_type/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/standards_space_type/</guid>
      <description>Best Practices for Space Type The SpaceType object in OpenStudio has the property StandardsSpaceType which can be used to identify the appropriate lighting space type. The lighting space type is used to determine the baseline lighting power density and lighting control savings based on Table G3.7 of 90.1 Appendix G. The lighting space type is also used for a number of other purposes in the baseline generation, including: determining special requirements for computer rooms and laboratories, identifying residential spaces, and determining applicability of receptacle control measures according to space type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Baseline generation API</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/prm_api_ref/baseline_generation_api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/prm_api_ref/baseline_generation_api/</guid>
      <description>The API functions for baseline generation including its arguments are as listed model_create_prm_stable_baseline_building model climate_zone default_hvac_bldg_type default_wwr_bldg_type default_swh_bldg_type output_dir unmet_load_hours debug Read the section below for a detailed breakdown of each function.
FUNCTION 1: model_create_prm_stable_baseline_building This is the primary API function to generate baseline models. The process involves taking a user-created OpenStudio model along with several user-defined arguments to produce a PRM baseline model. This function contains numerous arguments, many of which require specific enum values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Data API</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/prm_api_ref/userdata_api/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/prm_api_ref/userdata_api/</guid>
      <description>The API functions for user data including its arguments are as listed convert_userdata_csv_to_json userdata_dir output_dir load_userdata_to_standards_database generate_userdata_to_csv Read the section below for a detailed breakdown of each function.
FUNCTION 1: convert_userdata_csv_to_json The function converts user data from CSV format to JSON format, and it is typically called before loading the user data before baseline generation.
standard = Standard.build(&amp;#34;90.1-PRM-2019&amp;#34;) userdata_dir = &amp;#34;#{File.dirname(Dir.pwd)}/user_data&amp;#34; output_dir = &amp;#34;#{File.dirname(Dir.pwd)}/output&amp;#34; # Converts user data from .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/space/user_data_space/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/space/user_data_space/</guid>
      <description>User Data CSV File: userdata_space.csv (745 B) The user_data_space.csv file provides an alternative way to assign Appendix G lighting space types to the model. See model_requirements for additional information on lighting space types and the list of valid entries.
The user_data_space.csv file allows the application of multiple lighting space types to a single Space object in the model. Each lighting space type entered into the user_data_space_type.csv file must be paired with a fraction value to indicate the percentage of the floor area for spaces that is to be assigned to that lighting space type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Space type</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/space/user_data_space_type/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/space/user_data_space_type/</guid>
      <description>User Data CSV File: userdata_spacetype.csv (723 B) The user_data_space_type.csv file provides an alternative way to assign Appendix G lighting space types to the model. See model_requirements for additional information on lighting space types and the list of valid entries.
The user_data_space_type.csv file allows the application of multiple lighting space types to a single SpaceType object in the model. Each lighting space type entered into the user_data_space_type.csv file must be paired with a fraction value to indicate the percentage of the floor area for spaces that is to be assigned to that lighting space type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/building_type/user_data_building/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/building_type/user_data_building/</guid>
      <description>Building building_type_for_hvac building_type_for_swh building_type_for_wwr is_exempt_from_rotations Building User Data CSV File: userdata_building.csv (97 B) The user_data_building.csv contains compliance data for building compliance calculation. A sample of data record is shown below.
building_type_for_hvac This field is used to determine the baseline model&amp;rsquo;s HVAC system. It can be overwritten at the zone level (see the documentation for user_data_thermal_zone.csv). It should be set to one of the following values that best described the proposed model&amp;rsquo;s building type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thermal Zone</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/building_type/user_data_thermal_zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/building_type/user_data_thermal_zone/</guid>
      <description>User Data CSV File: userdata_thermal_zone.csv (114 B) File Name: userdata_thermal_zone.csv name: Name of the thermal zone object in the model.
building_type_for_hvac This is the building type designation used for determining the Appendix G baseline system type. Valid entries are:
residential public assembly heated-only storage retail other nonresidential unconditioned hospital number_of_systems This allows multiple systems to be modeled conceptually in a single thermal zone. This could be used when a single thermal zone in the model is used to represent multiple thermal zones in the actual building.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zone HVAC</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_zone_hvac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_zone_hvac/</guid>
      <description>Zone HVAC Pressure-drop adjustments has_fan_power_credit_fully_ducted has_fan_power_credit_return_or_exhaust_flow_control fan_power_credit_exhaust_treatment has_fan_power_credit_filtration_m9to12 has_fan_power_credit_filtration_m13to15 clean_filter_pressure_drop_for_fan_power_credit_filtration_m16plus fan_power_credit_gas_phase_cleaners fan_power_credit_biosafety fan_power_credit_other_than_coil_runaround has_fan_power_credit_coil_runaround fan_power_credit_evaporative_humidifier_or_cooler has_fan_power_credit_sound_attenuation has_fan_power_credit_exhaust_serving_fume_hoods has_fan_power_credit_lab_or_vivarium_highrise_vertical_duct Zone HVAC User Data CSV File: userdata_zone_hvac.csv (896 B) The user_data_zone_hvac.csv contains compliance data for zone HVAC compliance calculation. A sample of data record is shown below.
Pressure-drop adjustments The following fields can be used to indicate what pressure-drop adjustment devices are present in each zone HVAC object in the proposed model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zone Infiltration</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_zone_infiltration/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_zone_infiltration/</guid>
      <description> User Data CSV File: userdata_zone_infiltration.csv (19 B) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airloop HVAC</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_airloop_hvac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_airloop_hvac/</guid>
      <description>Airloop HVAC Pressure-drop adjustments has_fan_power_credit_fully_ducted has_fan_power_credit_return_or_exhaust_flow_control fan_power_credit_exhaust_treatment has_fan_power_credit_filtration_m9to12 has_fan_power_credit_filtration_m13to15 clean_filter_pressure_drop_for_fan_power_credit_filtration_m16plus fan_power_credit_gas_phase_cleaners fan_power_credit_biosafety fan_power_credit_other_than_coil_runaround has_fan_power_credit_coil_runaround fan_power_credit_evaporative_humidifier_or_cooler has_fan_power_credit_sound_attenuation has_fan_power_credit_exhaust_serving_fume_hoods has_fan_power_credit_lab_or_vivarium_highrise_vertical_duct Air-side economizer economizer_exception_for_gas_phase_air_cleaning economizer_exception_for_open_refrigerated_cases Exhaust air energy recovery exhaust_energy_recovery_exception_for_toxic_fumes_etc exhaust_energy_recovery_exception_for_type1_kitchen_hoods exhaust_energy_recovery_exception_for_type_distributed_exhaust exhaust_energy_recovery_exception_for_dehumidifcation_with_series_cooling_recovery Airloop HVAC User Data CSV File: userdata_airloop_hvac.csv (988 B) The user_data_airloop_hvac.csv contains compliance data for airloop HVAC compliance calculation. A sample of data record is shown below.
Pressure-drop adjustments The following fields can be used to indicate what pressure-drop adjustment devices are present in each airloop HVAC object in the proposed model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airloop HVAC DOAS</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_airloop_hvac_doas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_airloop_hvac_doas/</guid>
      <description>Airloop HVAC DOAS Pressure-drop adjustments has_fan_power_credit_fully_ducted has_fan_power_credit_return_or_exhaust_flow_control fan_power_credit_exhaust_treatment has_fan_power_credit_filtration_m9to12 has_fan_power_credit_filtration_m13to15 clean_filter_pressure_drop_for_fan_power_credit_filtration_m16plus fan_power_credit_gas_phase_cleaners fan_power_credit_biosafety fan_power_credit_other_than_coil_runaround has_fan_power_credit_coil_runaround fan_power_credit_evaporative_humidifier_or_cooler has_fan_power_credit_sound_attenuation has_fan_power_credit_exhaust_serving_fume_hoods has_fan_power_credit_lab_or_vivarium_highrise_vertical_duct Airloop HVAC DOAS User Data CSV File: userdata_airloop_hvac_doas.csv (611 B) The user_data_airloop_hvac_doas.csv contains compliance data for airloop HVAC DOAS compliance calculation. A sample of data record is shown below.
Pressure-drop adjustments The following fields can be used to indicate what pressure-drop adjustment devices are present in each airloop HVAC DOAS object in the proposed model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Outdoor Air</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_design_specification_outdoor_air/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/hvac/user_data_design_specification_outdoor_air/</guid>
      <description> User Data CSV File: userdata_design_specification_outdoor_air.csv (122 B) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electric Equipment</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/equipment/user_data_electric_equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/equipment/user_data_electric_equipment/</guid>
      <description> User Data CSV File: userdata_electric_equipment.csv (411 B) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gas Equipment</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/equipment/user_data_gas_equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/equipment/user_data_gas_equipment/</guid>
      <description> User Data CSV File: userdata_gas_equipment.csv (65 B) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lights</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/lighting/user_data_lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/lighting/user_data_lights/</guid>
      <description>Lights has_retail_display_exception has_unregulated_exception unregulated_category Lights User Data CSV File: userdata_lights.csv (81 B) The user_data_lights.csv contains compliance data for lights compliance calculation. A sample of data record is shown below.
has_retail_display_exception Set this field to yes if the lights object qualifies as display lighting: the lighting must be specifically designed and directed to highlight merchandise and separately controlled from the general lighting. If it doesn&amp;rsquo;t apply, leave this field blank or set to no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exterior Lights</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/lighting/user_data_exterior_lights/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 16:29:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/lighting/user_data_exterior_lights/</guid>
      <description>Exterior Lights end_use_subcategory Tradeable Exterior Lighting Subcategories Non-Tradeable Exterior Lighting Subcategories end_use_measurement_value Exterior Lights User Data CSV File: userdata_exterior_lights.csv (467 B) The user_data_exterior_lights.csv contains compliance data for exterior lighting compliance calculation. A sample of data record is shown below.
end_use_subcategory Each exterior lights object in the model can be assigned up to nine exterior lighting subcategories in the user data file based on Appendix G Table G3.6. The lighting subcategories are designated by the labels:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Connections</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/water/user_data_wateruse_connections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/water/user_data_wateruse_connections/</guid>
      <description> User Data CSV File: userdata_wateruse_connections.csv (82 B) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Equipment</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/water/user_data_wateruse_equipment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/water/user_data_wateruse_equipment/</guid>
      <description> User Data CSV File: userdata_wateruse_equipment.csv (22 B) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Water Equip Definition</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/water/user_data_wateruse_equipment_definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:06:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/add_compliance_data/water/user_data_wateruse_equipment_definition/</guid>
      <description> User Data CSV File: userdata_wateruse_equipment_definition.csv (76 B) </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
