<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Model requirements on OSSTD doc</title>
    <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Model requirements on OSSTD doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:04:10 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/best_practices/</guid>
      <description>Here are some best practices to run the PRM measure: The space types should be defined in the model : The lighting space type is used to determine the baseline lighting power density and lighting control savings. Read more about it in Standards space type section. If the User Compliance Data files contain lighting space type assignments, there is a hierachy for determining the final assignments:
user_data_space is first priority user_data_space_type is second priority StandardsSpaceType property of the SpaceType objest is lowest priority Dates in the schedule must have a &amp;ldquo;MM/DD&amp;rdquo; formatting : Where is this inserted?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standards space type</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/standards_space_type/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/standards_space_type/</guid>
      <description>Best Practices for Space Type The SpaceType object in OpenStudio has the property StandardsSpaceType which can be used to identify the appropriate lighting space type. The lighting space type is used to determine the baseline lighting power density and lighting control savings based on Table G3.7 of 90.1 Appendix G. The lighting space type is also used for a number of other purposes in the baseline generation, including: determining special requirements for computer rooms and laboratories, identifying residential spaces, and determining applicability of receptacle control measures according to space type.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
