<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Model requirements on OSSTD doc</title>
    <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Model requirements on OSSTD doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:04:10 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Best Practices</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/best_practices/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/best_practices/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Standards space type</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/standards_space_type/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:05:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/standards_space_type/</guid>
      <description>Standards Space Type The SpaceType object in OpenStudio has the property StandardsSpaceType which can be used to identify the appropriate lighting space type. The lighting space type is used to determine the baseline lighting power density and lighting control savings based on Table G3.7 of 90.1 Appendix G. The lighting space type is also used for a number of other purposes in the baseline generation, including: determining special requirements for computer rooms and laboratories, identifying residential spaces, and determining applicability of receptacle control measures according to space type.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Other requirements</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/other_requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 15:05:48 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/user_guide/model_requirements/other_requirements/</guid>
      <description>The user model should have occupancy control of lighting incorporated into the lighing use schedules where it is required by ASHRAE 90.1-2019. The program will back-calculate the uncontrolled lighting schedules for the Baseline model based on the occupancy sensor reduction values in Appendix G Table G3.7.
The user model needs to have a fully defined HVAC system. Most of the HVAC objects are deleted when the Appendix G Baseline is created, but some information is taken from the user model and transferred to the Baselne.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
