<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Use with OS SDK using CLI on OSSTD doc</title>
    <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Use with OS SDK using CLI on OSSTD doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:49:40 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Get OpenStudio SDK</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/get_openstudio_sdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/get_openstudio_sdk/</guid>
      <description>The OpenStudio SDK, managed by the NREL, provides a command line interface (CLI) to access OpenStudio&amp;rsquo;s functionality.
Installation Download the latest release of OpenStudio SDK from OpenStudio Releases GitHub page. Select the installer that matches your operating system.
The OpenStudio SDK installation package contains OpenStudio-Standards, EnergyPlus as well as other components (e.g., Ruby 2.7, etc..).
For more installation information, refer to the OpenStudio Github page.
Information about OpenStudio SDK CLI, refer to the Command Line Interface (CLI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run the measure</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_the_measure/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_the_measure/</guid>
      <description>Prerequisite Before running any measures, make sure you have OpenStudio SDK installed. The instruction and correct version can be found in Get OpenStudio SDK.
Download the PRM measure Download measure in the link below: Create Baseline Building: measures.zip (7 KB) Refer to Install the measure for other installation options.
Setup Setup a local directory to include all required inputs (the following example is one way to setup the directory):
Seed model: place the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run measure on source code</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_measure_with_osstd_package/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/os_cli/run_measure_with_osstd_package/</guid>
      <description>This instruction is provided for user who wants to access the latest features or bug fixes that are not accessible in the latest OpenStudio SDK. Follow the run measure instruction to setup your project folder.
Setup Download this openstudio-standards package. Unzip the package to a local directory.
Depends on which new feature you&amp;rsquo;d like to use, the download link could be different. See Github instruction on how to download source code</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
