<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Examples on OSSTD doc</title>
    <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Examples on OSSTD doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:50:09 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Demo 1: Geometry</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo1/</guid>
      <description>Demo 1 shows geometry transformations in a user model The proposed model (as shown in the image) is a typical medium sized office building with roughly 60% window-to-wall ratio (WWR) and overhangs on its south facade. The default_hvac_bldg_type is set to other nonresidential, and the window to wall ratio and service water heating system building types are both set according to the related category. The building is assumed to be located in New York City.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo 2: HVAC</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo2/</guid>
      <description>Demo 2 shows HVAC transformations in a user model In Demo 2, we have a medium office user model with an area of 52000 sqft. It is equipped with water source heat pumps for heating and cooling and a DOAS for ventilation (as shown in the image below). Also, the Core Top Zone is being identified as a high equipment density (40 W/m2) room.
According to the ASHRAE 90.1 PRM method - &amp;ldquo;Baseline HVAC System Types&amp;rdquo; table, the baseline system type for the medium office that satisfies the requirements - Other residential + 5 floors or fewer and 25000ft2 to 150,000ft2, shall be a packaged VAV with reheat (system 5).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demo 3: User Data</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:04:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/get_start/demo/demo3/</guid>
      <description>Demo 3 shows how to provide additional user data for the PRM function In Demo 3, we will demonstrate how to input user data to handle multiple building types in a model.
Download the folder &amp;ldquo;demo3_zip&amp;rdquo; on your system and extract it in any local folder (to be changed based on the method used in the sections below). The zip file contains the model (.osm), user data (.csv) and weather file (.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
