<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on OSSTD doc</title>
    <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on OSSTD doc</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 16:26:38 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Key Capabilities</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/capabilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:48:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/capabilities/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;Create ASHRAE 90.1-2019 PRM Model&amp;rdquo; measure provides a detailed implementation of the rules of the Appendix G Performance Rating Method. Below are some of the key changes that are applied by the tool when creating the Baseline model:
Apply baseline envelope rules Space conditioning type Constructions Insulation levels Window-to-wall ratio Skylight-to-roof ratio Infiltration Apply baseline lighting rules Lighting power Lighting occupancy sensor control Determine and create baseline HVAC systems Remove user model HVAC Determine baseline HVAC based on building type and Appendix G rules Create new baseline HVAC systems Apply special rules for computer rooms and laboratories Size HVAC systems Appl HVAC efficiencies Apply fan power adjustments Apply baseline HVAC controls Rotate building model through cardinal directions Check for unmet load hours and rectify, if needed Handle additional compliance data Multiple building types Plug load measures Elevators Exterior lighting Interior lighting exceptions Number of systems per zone </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limitations</title>
      <link>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/limitations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2022 14:48:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pnnl.github.io/BEM-for-PRM/overview/limitations/</guid>
      <description>Some features of 90.1-2019 Appendix G that have not yet been implemenented into the baseline automation are as follows:
Baseline humidification is same as user model in the current tool. In some cases the baseline is required to be changed to adiabatic humidification. This has not been implemented. Baseline dehumidification is same as user model in the current tool. For constant volume systems, Appendix G indicates that only 25% of the system reheat energy shall be included in the budget building performance.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
